k9stud.com 2014-07-18

# k9Stud.com

|  **Information Collection and Use**   
K9Stud.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.   
---  
**Registration**   
To begin using our services, you must first register by clicking on the “Sign Up” button which is located on the homepage. During registration a user is required to give their contact information, such as name and email address. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.   
**Cookies**   
Our homepage has the option to use a cookie (Remember Me) to facilitate the members’ memory of their username when logging on to the site.   
**Log Files**   
We use IP addresses to investigate fraud activities if they are occurring on the site. We do not use IP addresses to gather personal information, such as ISP, country, etc.   
**Sharing**   
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.   
**Credit Card**   
We use Card Service International services to handle the credit card processing to bill users for goods and services.   
**Links**   
K9Stud.com is not responsible for the information contained on other sites through links on our site. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by K9sStud.com.   
**Security**   
K9stud.com will safeguard all its members’ information. When members submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected. As a member chooses to upgrade their account, all information on the form such as credit card, name and location travels through an SSL tunnel using 128 bit encryption. In addition, you can check the websites authenticity at www.geotrust.com to ensure our certificate is up to date. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to K9Stud@K9Stud.com.   
**Scammers, Spammers, Abusers and Hackers**   
K9Stud.com will display the following information publicly on the website when rules, abuse, hacking attempts and intent in harming any advertiser or staff member takes place: IP address, Email, Name, City, State, Country and Zip.   
**E-Mail Promotions and Special Offers**   
We may send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive our monthly e-mail messages and information on products, services, special deals, and a monthly photo contest.   
**Unsubscribing**   
Members are given the opportunity to unsubscribe from our e-mail messages and special offers email communications by clicking on the “Contact Us” link located on the bottom of every page on K9Stud.com. Please note that by using our service and posting classified ads, Members will receive emails from parties interested in the pet, product or service that User is advertising.   
**Notification of Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
